{
    "subject": "resource/Samuel_Hoare,_1st_Viscount_Templewood",
    "predicate": "ontology/almaMater",
    "object": "resource/New_College,_Oxford",
    "human_readable": "Samuel Hoare, 1st Viscount Templewood's alma mater is New College, Oxford.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.969475507736206,
            "question": "Is New College, Oxford associated with Samuel Hoare?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8583204746246338,
            "question": "Which institution is known as the alma mater of Samuel Hoare?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8309868574142456,
            "question": "What is the alma mater of the 1st Viscount Templewood?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7263889908790588,
            "question": "What was the name of Samuel Hoare's educational institution?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7127725481987,
            "question": "What is the full name of Samuel Hoare's educational institution?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7009521126747131,
            "question": "Who studied at New College, Oxford?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6426604390144348,
            "question": "At what university did Samuel Hoare study?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6051074862480164,
            "question": "To which university did Samuel Hoare go to school?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5853352546691895,
            "question": "What was Samuel Hoare's title?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5299579501152039,
            "question": "Where did Samuel Hoare receive his education?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Samuel Hoare, 1st Viscount Templewood's alma mater is New College, Oxford.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6330_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was Samuel Hoare's title?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6330_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To which university did Samuel Hoare go to school?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6330_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=At what university did Samuel Hoare study?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6330_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6330_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6330_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6330_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6330_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6330_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6330_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6330_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6330_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6330_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6330_75.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents confirms that Samuel Hoare, 1st Viscount Templewood was educated at Harrow and later attended New College, Oxford. This is mentioned in multiple documents (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6330/re-ranker-msmarco/25.txt, file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6330/re-ranker-msmarco/43.txt, and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6330/re-ranker-msmarco/55.txt)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Sir Samuel Hoare, 1st Viscount Templewood, including his education at Harrow and New College, Oxford. This supports the statement that his alma mater was New College, Oxford."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}